<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addons>
    <addon id="plugin.video.csfd-rebricek" name="ČSFD Rebríček" version="12.10.2" provider-name="CSFD-SC-Bridge">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Browse ČSFD top rankings and open in Stream Cinema</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Rebríčky filmov a seriálov z ČSFD s otvorením vo Stream Cinema</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Žebříčky filmů a seriálů z ČSFD s otevřením ve Stream Cinema</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">Browse top movies, series and seasons from ČSFD rankings filtered by year. Each item shows rating, plot and reviews. Click any title to instantly search it in Stream Cinema.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Prehliadaj rebríčky filmov, seriálov a sérií z ČSFD s filtrom od roku. Každá položka zobrazuje hodnotenie, plot a recenzie. Kliknutím na titul sa otvorí vyhľadávanie priamo vo Stream Cinema.</description>
            <description lang="cs">Procházej žebříčky filmů, seriálů a sérií z ČSFD s filtrem od roku. Každá položka zobrazuje hodnocení, popis a recenze. Kliknutím na titul se otevře vyhledávání přímo ve Stream Cinema.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.csfd-rebricek.lite" name="CSFD Rebricek Lite" version="1.0.0" provider-name="CSFD-SC-Bridge">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Lightweight CSFD rankings for Stream Cinema</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Odlahcene CSFD rebricky pre Stream Cinema</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Odlehcene CSFD zebricky pro Stream Cinema</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">A lighter CSFD rankings addon tuned for faster home widgets and smaller ranking pages while keeping direct Stream Cinema search.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Odlahceny addon s CSFD rebrickami upraveny pre rychlejsie home widgety a mensie stranky rebrickov pri zachovani priameho vyhladavania v Stream Cinema.</description>
            <description lang="cs">Odlehceny addon s CSFD zebricky upraveny pro rychlejsi home widgety a mensi stranky zebricku pri zachovani primeho vyhledavani ve Stream Cinema.</description>
            <news>v1.0.0 (2026-04-08)
     - Added a Lite variant with smaller pages and lower worker pressure
     - Tuned ranking cache retention for faster repeated home loads
     - Kept CSFD metadata and direct Stream Cinema opening behavior
            </news>
            <platform>all</platform>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.kolop" name="Kolop" version="1.2.3" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Stream Cinema movies and series sorted by CSFD rating</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Filmy a serialy zo Stream Cinema zoradene podla CSFD</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Filmy a serialy ze Stream Cinema serazene podle CSFD</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">Loads new and recently added Stream Cinema movies and series, matches them against CSFD, enriches them with rating, votes, plot and reviews, then sorts the list in a CSFD-style order with cached widget results for faster home loading.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Nacita novinky a najnovsie pridane filmy a serialy zo Stream Cinema, sparuje ich s CSFD, doplni hodnotenie, hlasy, obsah a recenzie a potom ich zoradi v style CSFD. Pre home widgety pouziva vyslednu disk cache, aby sa nacitali rychlejsie.</description>
            <description lang="cs">Nacte novinky a nejnoveji pridane filmy a serialy ze Stream Cinema, sparuje je s CSFD, doplni hodnoceni, hlasy, obsah a recenze a potom je seradi ve stylu CSFD. Pro home widgety pouziva vyslednou disk cache, aby se nacitaly rychleji.</description>
            <news>v1.2.3 (2026-04-08)
     - Startup prewarm now stays disabled automatically when skin.kolop.lite is the active skin
     - This keeps the full and lite Kolop stacks from warming in parallel on the same Kodi boot
    v1.2.2 (2026-04-07)
     - Corrected movie widget mapping so Novinky use the original Stream Cinema latest feed and Novinky dabovane use the original latestd feed
     - Kept the dubbed movie feed prewarmed for skin.kolop while removing it from the addon root menu
    v1.2.1 (2026-04-07)
     - Added a dedicated dubbed movie releases source sorted through CSFD for skin.kolop home widgets
     - Prewarm now covers dubbed movie news so the extra row is ready sooner after Kodi startup
    v1.2.0 (2026-04-07)
     - Added Android-friendly startup prewarm and retry handling so Kolop widgets recover on cold Kodi boots
     - Added CSFD-based Tips of the Day sources for movies and series
     - Kept widget caches warm in the background through a Kodi service entry point
    v1.1.2 (2026-04-07)
     - Reduced Kolop widget fallback and detail cache retention from 3 days to 20 hours
     - Kept CSFD-driven home ordering while shortening stale widget lifetime
    v1.1.1 (2026-04-07)
     - Home widgets in skin.kolop now expose 25 items and keep last watched sections for SC movies and series
     - Switched JSON cache writes to an atomic temp-file replace flow to avoid corrupted detail/search cache files
     - Replaced fragile strptime date parsing so the recent-series widget works reliably on Kodi runtime
    v1.1.0 (2026-04-07)
     - Added movie and series sources for new and recently added Stream Cinema content
     - Added cached widget payloads for faster home loading
     - Added dedicated skin.kolop integration and improved metadata for repository publishing
    v1.0.1 (2026-04-06)
     - Switched CSFD requests to a safer header strategy that avoids the current anti-bot challenge in normal flow
     - Removed shared HTTP session usage across worker threads
     - Serialized cache updates for parallel CSFD search/detail enrichment
            </news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.kolop.lite" name="Kolop Lite" version="1.0.0" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Lite Stream Cinema movies and series sorted by CSFD rating</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Odlahcena verzia Stream Cinema filmov a serialov zoradenych podla CSFD</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Odlehcena verze Stream Cinema filmu a serialu serazenych podle CSFD</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">A lighter Kolop variant focused on faster Kodi startup. It keeps CSFD-sorted movie and series rows, trims the home payload, and prewarms only the most important widgets.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Odlahcena verzia Kolopu zamerana na rychlejsi start Kodi. Zachovava CSFD zoradenie pre filmy a serialy, zmensuje home payload a prewarmuje iba najdolezitejsie widgety.</description>
            <description lang="cs">Odlehcena verze Kolopu zamerena na rychlejsi start Kodi. Zachovava CSFD razeni pro filmy a serialy, zmensuje home payload a prewarmuje jen nejdulezitejsi widgety.</description>
            <news>v1.0.0 (2026-04-08)
     - Added a startup-focused Lite variant with a lower default item limit and smaller prewarm set
     - Kept CSFD-sorted movie and series widgets while trimming the default home workload
     - Limited background warmup to the most important rows for faster cold starts
            </news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.lolop.cs" name="Lolop CS" version="1.0.0" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Combined Stream Cinema and CSFD rankings in one addon</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Kombinovany Stream Cinema a CSFD rebricek v jednom addone</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Kombinovany Stream Cinema a CSFD zebricek v jednom addonu</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">All-in-one Lolop CS addon: Stream Cinema sources sorted by CSFD plus full CSFD rankings (movies, series, seasons) with year filter. Powers skin.lolop.cs without needing two separate addons.</description>
            <description lang="sk">All-in-one Lolop CS addon: Stream Cinema zdroje zoradene podla CSFD plus plne CSFD rebricky (filmy, serialy, serie) s filtrom od roku. Pohana skin.lolop.cs bez potreby dvoch samostatnych addonov.</description>
            <description lang="cs">All-in-one Lolop CS addon: Stream Cinema zdroje serazene podle CSFD plus plne CSFD zebricky (filmy, serialy, serie) s filtrem od roku. Pohani skin.lolop.cs bez potreby dvou samostatnych addonu.</description>
            <news>v1.0.0 (2026-04-25)
     - Initial release combining plugin.video.kolop and plugin.video.csfd-rebricek into a single addon
     - Provides both CSFD-sorted Stream Cinema sources and full CSFD ranking browsing
     - Powers skin.lolop.cs so only one addon is required instead of two
            </news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="plugin.video.lolop.cs.lite" name="Lolop CS Lite" version="1.0.0" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="21.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup4" version="4.9.3" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
            <provides>video</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Lite combined Stream Cinema and CSFD rankings in one addon</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Odlahceny Stream Cinema a CSFD rebricek v jednom addone</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Odlehceny Stream Cinema a CSFD zebricek v jednom addonu</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">Lite all-in-one Lolop CS addon: trimmed Stream Cinema sources sorted by CSFD plus full CSFD rankings (movies, series, seasons) with year filter. Powers skin.lolop.cs.lite without needing two separate addons.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Odlahceny all-in-one Lolop CS addon: zostriatne Stream Cinema zdroje zoradene podla CSFD plus plne CSFD rebricky (filmy, serialy, serie) s filtrom od roku. Pohana skin.lolop.cs.lite bez potreby dvoch samostatnych addonov.</description>
            <description lang="cs">Odlehceny all-in-one Lolop CS addon: zkracene Stream Cinema zdroje serazene podle CSFD plus plne CSFD zebricky (filmy, serialy, serie) s filtrem od roku. Pohani skin.lolop.cs.lite bez potreby dvou samostatnych addonu.</description>
            <news>v1.0.0 (2026-04-25)
     - Initial release combining plugin.video.kolop.lite and plugin.video.csfd-rebricek.lite into a single addon
     - Provides both CSFD-sorted Stream Cinema sources and full CSFD ranking browsing
     - Powers skin.lolop.cs.lite so only one addon is required instead of two
            </news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-or-later</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="repository.42polol" name="42po.lol Repository" version="1.0.5" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="42po.lol Repository">
            <dir>
                <info compressed="false">https://42po.lol/addons.xml</info>
                <checksum algo="md5">https://42po.lol/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
                <datadir zip="true">https://42po.lol/</datadir>
            </dir>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="sk">CS Kodi repozitár</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">CS Kodi repozitář</summary>
            <summary lang="en">CS Kodi repository</summary>
            <description lang="sk">CS kodi repo - ČSFD Rebríček a Titulky DualSub</description>
            <description lang="en">CS kodi repo - ČSFD Rankings and Titulky DualSub</description>
            <news>v1.0.5
    - Rebuild repository ZIP with Kodi-compatible classic ZIP metadata</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.lolop-logsender" name="Lolop Log Sender" version="0.1.2" provider-name="Codex">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py">
            <provides>executable</provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Send Kodi logs to the TitDeepL helper</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">Small diagnostic addon for Android and Xbox Kodi. It sends kodi.log and kodi.old.log to the configured TitDeepL helper so update failures can be inspected remotely.</description>
            <news>v0.1.2
    - Publish web-visible icon/fanart paths and rebuild package with Kodi-safe ZIP metadata</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>MIT</license>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.titdeepl-localsub" name="TitDeepL LocalSub" version="0.1.20" provider-name="Codex">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="default.py">
            <provides>
                <subtitle>
                    <language>cs</language>
                    <language>sk</language>
                    <language>uk</language>
                </subtitle>
            </provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" />
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Translate CZ/SK subtitles and queue remote OpenSubtitles upload</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">Finds nearby subtitle files, reuses cached Ukrainian translations from a remote helper when available, otherwise translates them with the DeepL API, produces bilingual ASS subtitles, and can queue the Ukrainian upload on a remote helper such as LibreELEC on Raspberry Pi.</description>
            <news>v0.1.20
    - Save finished dual ASS subtitles to the helper cache
    - Offer saved helper dualsubs first in the subtitle search window
    - Match saved dualsubs by IMDb, release/title fallback, and TV episode key</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>MIT</license>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.titulky-deepl" name="Titulky DeepL" version="0.5.1" provider-name="Codex">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="default.py">
            <provides>
                <subtitle>
                    <language>cs</language>
                    <language>sk</language>
                    <language>uk</language>
                </subtitle>
            </provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Create Czech/Slovak plus Ukrainian bilingual subtitles with DeepL</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">Finds nearby or currently loaded subtitle files, sends their subtitle text to the DeepL API, writes a bilingual subtitle file that keeps the original lines and adds Ukrainian translations underneath, then returns it through Kodi's subtitle search flow.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>MIT</license>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.titulky-deepl-sub" name="Titulky DeepL Sub" version="0.3.0" provider-name="Codex">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="default.py">
            <provides>
                <subtitle>
                    <language>uk</language>
                </subtitle>
            </provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_gb">Translate CZ/SK subtitles to Ukrainian with DeepL and upload to OpenSubtitles</summary>
            <description lang="en_gb">Finds nearby subtitle files, translates them to Ukrainian using DeepL API, produces bilingual ASS subtitles (original top + Ukrainian bottom), and optionally uploads the Ukrainian translation to OpenSubtitles.org via browser automation.</description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>MIT</license>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.titulky-dualsub" name="Titulky DualSub (OpenSubtitles + Titulky.com)" version="1.5.1" provider-name="community">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
            <import addon="script.module.chardet" version="2.3.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.pysubs2" version="1.3.1" optional="true" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="service.py">
            <provides>
                <subtitle>
                    <language>af</language>
                    <language>sq</language>
                    <language>ar</language>
                    <language>hy</language>
                    <language>bs</language>
                    <language>bg</language>
                    <language>ca</language>
                    <language>zh</language>
                    <language>hr</language>
                    <language>cs</language>
                    <language>da</language>
                    <language>nl</language>
                    <language>en</language>
                    <language>eo</language>
                    <language>et</language>
                    <language>fi</language>
                    <language>fr</language>
                    <language>de</language>
                    <language>el</language>
                    <language>he</language>
                    <language>hi</language>
                    <language>hu</language>
                    <language>id</language>
                    <language>it</language>
                    <language>ja</language>
                    <language>ko</language>
                    <language>lv</language>
                    <language>lt</language>
                    <language>mk</language>
                    <language>ms</language>
                    <language>no</language>
                    <language>fa</language>
                    <language>pl</language>
                    <language>pt</language>
                    <language>ro</language>
                    <language>ru</language>
                    <language>sr</language>
                    <language>sk</language>
                    <language>sl</language>
                    <language>es</language>
                    <language>sv</language>
                    <language>ta</language>
                    <language>th</language>
                    <language>tr</language>
                    <language>uk</language>
                    <language>vi</language>
                </subtitle>
            </provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en">Search and download dual subtitles from OpenSubtitles.com, Titulky.com, and TVsubtitles.net simultaneously</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Vyhľadávanie a sťahovanie duálnych titulkov z OpenSubtitles.com, Titulky.com a TVsubtitles.net súčasne</summary>
            <summary lang="cs">Hledání a stahování duálních titulků z OpenSubtitles.com, Titulky.com a TVsubtitles.net současně</summary>
            <description lang="en">
                Combines OpenSubtitles.com, Titulky.com and TVsubtitles.net into a single dual-subtitle addon.
                Searches all sources in parallel. Select two subtitles — first selected appears at the TOP (white),
                second at the BOTTOM (yellow). Supports Ukrainian, English, and 40+ languages.
                TVsubtitles.net is searched automatically for TV shows (Ukrainian, English and others — not Czech/Slovak).
                Requires OpenSubtitles.com and/or Titulky.com credentials in addon settings.
            </description>
            <description lang="sk">
                Kombinuje zdroje titulkov OpenSubtitles.com, Titulky.com a TVsubtitles.net do jedného duálneho addonu.
                Vyhľadáva všetky zdroje paralelne. Vyber dva titulky — prvý vybraný ide HORE (biele),
                druhý vybraný ide DOLE (žlté). TVsubtitles.net sa prehľadáva automaticky pre seriály
                (ukrajinčina, angličtina a ďalšie — nie čeština/slovenčina).
            </description>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
            <source>https://github.com/</source>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="service.subtitles.titulky-dualsub-phoneticua" name="Titulky Phonetic UA" version="1.6.6" provider-name="community">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
            <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1" />
            <import addon="script.module.chardet" version="2.3.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="service.py">
            <provides>
                <subtitle>
                    <language>cs</language>
                    <language>sk</language>
                    <language>uk</language>
                </subtitle>
            </provides>
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Download Czech or Slovak subtitles and auto-build a Ukrainian phonetic dual subtitle</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">
                Downloads Czech or Slovak subtitles from OpenSubtitles.com or Titulky.com.
                After selecting one subtitle, the add-on generates a Ukrainian phonetic version locally
                and merges both into one dual subtitle file with one line on top and one on bottom.
            </description>
            <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Requires configured provider accounts for the subtitle source you use.</disclaimer>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
            <source>https://github.com/</source>
            <news>v1.6.6 (2026-04-03)
     - Added a separate Slovak style switch: Simple (recommended) or Precise
     - Simple Slovak mode now favors faster reading in Cyrillic over narrower phonetic detail
    v1.6.5 (2026-04-03)
     - Split phonetic rewriting into clearer Czech and Slovak profiles
     - Auto mode now locks one profile for the whole subtitle instead of mixing by word
    v1.6.4 (2026-04-03)
     - Improved Czech and Slovak phonetic rewrite rules using updated practical-transcription research
     - Better handling for Czech ě, Slovak ia/ie/iu, soft consonants, and Ji- forms
    v1.6.3 (2026-04-01)
     - Swapped subtitle lanes so Czech or Slovak is shown on top and Ukrainian phonetic on bottom
    v1.6.2 (2026-03-31)
     - Repackaged build after Raspberry Pi search-speed improvements
    v1.6.1 (2026-03-31)
     - Added fast search mode for slower devices such as Raspberry Pi
     - Added shorter network timeouts and stopped waiting on slow providers
     - Reused cached file metadata and skipped remote movie hashing in fast mode
    v1.6.0 (2026-03-31)
     - Cleaned the standalone addon down to a single search-download-rewrite-merge flow
     - Removed legacy multi-select and TVSubtitles leftovers
     - One selected Czech or Slovak subtitle now downloads, generates phonetic Ukrainian, and merges automatically</news>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="skin.kolop" version="1.1.7" name="Kolop Skin" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0" />
            <import addon="plugin.video.kolop" version="1.2.2" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
            <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Dedicated Kolop skin with fast home widgets</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Samostatny Kolop skin s rychlymi home widgetmi</summary>
            <summary lang="cs_CZ">Samostatny Kolop skin s rychlymi home widgety</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">A dedicated Kodi skin for Kolop focused on fast startup, lazy home widgets, and CSFD-sorted movies and series.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Samostatny Kodi skin pre Kolop zamerany na rychly start, lazy home widgety a filmy so serialmi zoradenymi podla CSFD.</description>
            <description lang="cs_CZ">Samostatny Kodi skin pro Kolop zamereny na rychly start, lazy home widgety a filmy se serialy serazenymi podle CSFD.</description>
            <news>v1.1.5 (2026-04-08)
     - Reworked Skin Settings so the visible Kolop and Stream Cinema options now map to the active home sections instead of the legacy Estuary home toggles
     - Unified the autoscroll setting key across the skin so the Auto Scroll toggle affects the related list, poster, fanart and PVR views consistently
    v1.1.4 (2026-04-07)
     - SC Filmy now keeps Novinky dabovane directly under Posledne sledovane and reads them from the original Stream Cinema category source
     - Removed the extra dubbed shortcut from the Kolop search dialog and kept the home rows aligned with the original SC sections
    v1.1.3 (2026-04-07)
     - Added a dedicated dubbed new releases row to SC Filmy using the Kolop CSFD-sorted source
     - Added matching labels and info-widget support for the new dubbed movie row
    v1.1.2 (2026-04-07)
     - Enabled media item ratings by default on first start
     - Increased the Kolop home plot area so longer descriptions fit
    v1.1.1 (2026-04-07)
     - Trimmed the custom SC home back so only Kategorie stays above the original Kolop rows
     - Removed the extra added home sections that were not requested
    v1.1.0 (2026-04-07)
     - Restored a wider Estuary Mod style home widget stack for SC movies and series
     - Added localized Kolop home labels and Czech-ready strings for the custom skin sections
     - Wired the new Kolop Tips of the Day widgets into home and info panels
    v1.0.3 (2026-04-07)
     - Read CSFD ratings explicitly via ListItem.Rating(csfd) and ListItem.Votes(csfd) in the home info widget
     - Show rating source as csfd.cz in the CSFD home info panel
    v1.0.2 (2026-04-07)
     - Moved the CSFD section to the end of the home menu
     - Added rating type display to the CSFD home info panel
    v1.0.1 (2026-04-07)
     - Restored home sections to CSFD, SC Filmy, SC Serialy and kept Doplnky visible by default
     - Added back last watched widgets for SC movies and series
     - Increased Kolop home widget limits to 25 items and kept CSFD integration on home/search
    		</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="skin.kolop.lite" version="1.0.4" name="Kolop Skin Lite" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0" />
            <import addon="plugin.video.kolop.lite" version="1.0.0" />
            <import addon="plugin.video.csfd-rebricek.lite" version="1.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
            <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Lightweight Kolop skin with smaller home rows</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Odlahceny Kolop skin s mensimi home riadkami</summary>
            <summary lang="cs_CZ">Odlehceny Kolop skin s mensimi home radky</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">A lite Kodi skin for Kolop focused on faster startup, smaller home rows, and CSFD-sorted movies and series through the lite addons.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Odlahceny Kodi skin pre Kolop zamerany na rychlejsi start, mensie home riadky a filmy so serialmi zoradenymi podla CSFD cez lite addony.</description>
            <description lang="cs_CZ">Odlehceny Kodi skin pro Kolop zamereny na rychlejsi start, mensi home radky a filmy se serialy serazenymi podle CSFD pres lite addony.</description>
            <news>v1.0.2 (2026-04-08)
     - Reworked Skin Settings so the visible Kolop and Stream Cinema options match the active Lite home sections
     - Unified the autoscroll setting key across the Lite skin so the Auto Scroll toggle affects the related list, poster, fanart and PVR views consistently
    v1.0.1 (2026-04-08)
     - Enabled the CSFD section by default on first start in the Lite skin
    v1.0.0 (2026-04-08)
     - Added a Lite skin variant that keeps the core Kolop sections but trims the active home rows
     - Reduced home row limits to 15 items and removed the newest-added rows from the default home flow
     - Switched the skin integration to the dedicated Kolop Lite and CSFD Lite addons
    		</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="skin.lolop.cs" version="1.0.0" name="Lolop CS Skin" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0" />
            <import addon="plugin.video.lolop.cs" version="1.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
            <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Single-addon Kolop skin with CSFD rankings built in</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Skin Kolop ktoremu staci jeden addon a obsahuje CSFD rebricky</summary>
            <summary lang="cs_CZ">Skin Kolop kteremu staci jeden addon a obsahuje CSFD zebricky</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">A Kodi skin for Lolop CS that bundles Stream Cinema sources and CSFD rankings into one required addon (plugin.video.lolop.cs). Faster startup and no need to install separate Kolop and CSFD addons.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Kodi skin pre Lolop CS ktory spaja Stream Cinema zdroje a CSFD rebricky do jedineho povinneho addonu (plugin.video.lolop.cs). Rychlejsi start a netreba samostatne instalovat Kolop a CSFD addony.</description>
            <description lang="cs_CZ">Kodi skin pro Lolop CS ktery spojuje Stream Cinema zdroje a CSFD zebricky do jedineho povinneho addonu (plugin.video.lolop.cs). Rychlejsi start a netreba samostatne instalovat Kolop a CSFD addony.</description>
            <news>v1.0.0 (2026-04-25)
     - Initial release based on skin.kolop
     - Switched all widget URLs to the new combined plugin.video.lolop.cs addon
     - Removed dependency on separate plugin.video.kolop and plugin.video.csfd-rebricek
    		</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
    <addon id="skin.lolop.cs.lite" version="1.0.0" name="Lolop CS Skin Lite" provider-name="lolop24">
        <requires>
            <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0" />
            <import addon="plugin.video.lolop.cs.lite" version="1.0.0" />
        </requires>
        <extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
            <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
        </extension>
        <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
            <summary lang="en_GB">Single-addon lite Kolop skin with CSFD rankings built in</summary>
            <summary lang="sk">Odlahceny skin Kolop ktoremu staci jeden addon</summary>
            <summary lang="cs_CZ">Odlehceny skin Kolop kteremu staci jeden addon</summary>
            <description lang="en_GB">A lite Kodi skin for Lolop CS that bundles trimmed Stream Cinema sources and CSFD rankings into one required addon (plugin.video.lolop.cs.lite). Smaller home rows, faster startup, no need to install separate Kolop and CSFD addons.</description>
            <description lang="sk">Odlahceny Kodi skin pre Lolop CS ktory spaja zostriatne Stream Cinema zdroje a CSFD rebricky do jedineho povinneho addonu (plugin.video.lolop.cs.lite). Mensie home riadky, rychlejsi start, netreba samostatne instalovat Kolop a CSFD addony.</description>
            <description lang="cs_CZ">Odlehceny Kodi skin pro Lolop CS ktery spojuje zkracene Stream Cinema zdroje a CSFD zebricky do jedineho povinneho addonu (plugin.video.lolop.cs.lite). Mensi home radky, rychlejsi start, netreba samostatne instalovat Kolop a CSFD addony.</description>
            <news>v1.0.0 (2026-04-25)
     - Initial release based on skin.kolop.lite
     - Switched all widget URLs to the new combined plugin.video.lolop.cs.lite addon
     - Removed dependency on separate plugin.video.kolop.lite and plugin.video.csfd-rebricek.lite
    		</news>
            <platform>all</platform>
            <license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
            <source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
            <assets>
                <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
                <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
                <screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
            </assets>
        </extension>
    </addon>
</addons>
