<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.kolop.lite" version="1.0.3" name="Kolop Skin Lite" provider-name="lolop24">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.17.0"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.kolop.lite" version="1.0.0"/>
		<import addon="plugin.video.csfd-rebricek.lite" version="1.0.0"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="xml" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="en_GB">Lightweight Kolop skin with smaller home rows</summary>
		<summary lang="sk">Odlahceny Kolop skin s mensimi home riadkami</summary>
		<summary lang="cs_CZ">Odlehceny Kolop skin s mensimi home radky</summary>
		<description lang="en_GB">A lite Kodi skin for Kolop focused on faster startup, smaller home rows, and CSFD-sorted movies and series through the lite addons.</description>
		<description lang="sk">Odlahceny Kodi skin pre Kolop zamerany na rychlejsi start, mensie home riadky a filmy so serialmi zoradenymi podla CSFD cez lite addony.</description>
		<description lang="cs_CZ">Odlehceny Kodi skin pro Kolop zamereny na rychlejsi start, mensi home radky a filmy se serialy serazenymi podle CSFD pres lite addony.</description>
		<news>v1.0.2 (2026-04-08)
 - Reworked Skin Settings so the visible Kolop and Stream Cinema options match the active Lite home sections
 - Unified the autoscroll setting key across the Lite skin so the Auto Scroll toggle affects the related list, poster, fanart and PVR views consistently
v1.0.1 (2026-04-08)
 - Enabled the CSFD section by default on first start in the Lite skin
v1.0.0 (2026-04-08)
 - Added a Lite skin variant that keeps the core Kolop sections but trims the active home rows
 - Reduced home row limits to 15 items and removed the newest-added rows from the default home flow
 - Switched the skin integration to the dedicated Kolop Lite and CSFD Lite addons
		</news>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<license>CC BY-SA 4.0, GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE Version 2.0</license>
		<source>https://github.com/lolop24/kodi-repo</source>
		<assets>
			<icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
			<fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-01.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-02.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-03.jpg</screenshot>
			<screenshot>resources/screenshot-04.jpg</screenshot>
		</assets>
	</extension>
</addon>
