<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.subtitles.titulky-dualsub-phoneticua"
       name="Titulky Phonetic UA"
       version="1.6.6"
       provider-name="community">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.9.1"/>
        <import addon="script.module.chardet" version="2.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="service.py">
        <provides>
            <subtitle>
                <language>cs</language>
                <language>sk</language>
                <language>uk</language>
            </subtitle>
        </provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en_GB">Download Czech or Slovak subtitles and auto-build a Ukrainian phonetic dual subtitle</summary>
        <description lang="en_GB">
            Downloads Czech or Slovak subtitles from OpenSubtitles.com or Titulky.com.
            After selecting one subtitle, the add-on generates a Ukrainian phonetic version locally
            and merges both into one dual subtitle file with one line on top and one on bottom.
        </description>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Requires configured provider accounts for the subtitle source you use.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <source>https://github.com/</source>
        <news>v1.6.6 (2026-04-03)
 - Added a separate Slovak style switch: Simple (recommended) or Precise
 - Simple Slovak mode now favors faster reading in Cyrillic over narrower phonetic detail
v1.6.5 (2026-04-03)
 - Split phonetic rewriting into clearer Czech and Slovak profiles
 - Auto mode now locks one profile for the whole subtitle instead of mixing by word
v1.6.4 (2026-04-03)
 - Improved Czech and Slovak phonetic rewrite rules using updated practical-transcription research
 - Better handling for Czech ě, Slovak ia/ie/iu, soft consonants, and Ji- forms
v1.6.3 (2026-04-01)
 - Swapped subtitle lanes so Czech or Slovak is shown on top and Ukrainian phonetic on bottom
v1.6.2 (2026-03-31)
 - Repackaged build after Raspberry Pi search-speed improvements
v1.6.1 (2026-03-31)
 - Added fast search mode for slower devices such as Raspberry Pi
 - Added shorter network timeouts and stopped waiting on slow providers
 - Reused cached file metadata and skipped remote movie hashing in fast mode
v1.6.0 (2026-03-31)
 - Cleaned the standalone addon down to a single search-download-rewrite-merge flow
 - Removed legacy multi-select and TVSubtitles leftovers
 - One selected Czech or Slovak subtitle now downloads, generates phonetic Ukrainian, and merges automatically</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
